&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：记住BigInt，它们是一个原始类型。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Remember BigInts, they're a primitive type.
因此，当您使用文字赋值BigInt时，例如第2行，
So when you assign a BigInt using a literal, for example like line 2,
42N不仅仅是数字42，而是在这个空间中可以增长的42
42n is not just the number 42, but it's 42 within this space where it can grow
本质上是无限大的，当然，直到系统上的内存空间。
essentially infinitely large, up to the memory space on the system, of course.
它本质上可以有一个无限大的整数。
It can essentially have an integer that grows infinitely large.
那是一个单独的分区
That's a separate partition,
它不是像JavaScript中所有其他数字一样的IEEE数字。
it's not an IEEE number like all the other numbers in JavaScript.
而且你必须非常小心，因为BigInt和常规数字，
And you have to be very careful, because BigInts and regular numbers,
它们并不是真的混合和匹配得很好。
they don't really mix and match that well.
它们是完全分开的东西，如果你愿意的话。
They're totally separated things, if you will.
所以如果我们有一样东西看起来
And so it's gonna be really useful for us if we have a thing that looks
像一个数字来确定它是一个数字，还是一个BigInt？
like a number to determine is that a number, or is it a BigInt?
这就是为什么TypeOf，至少现在，
Which is why typeof, at least at the moment,
将返回字符串BigInt。
is slated to return us the string, BigInt.